globusstores.com 2012-06-21

# Privacy Policy | Globus

Globus Stores Pvt Ltd including www.globus.in, respects your privacy. This Privacy Policy outlines the manner your data is collected and used by SSL. You are advised to please read the Privacy Policy carefully. By accessing the services provided by www.globus.in you agree to the collection and use of your data by www.globus.in in the manner provided in this Privacy Policy.

The Policy does not apply to the procedures and practices followed by entities that are not managed, owned or controlled by www.globus.in or to the people that are not engaged, employed or managed by www.globus.in  

All Contents on the Site is the sole property of www.globus.in or its owners. We authorize you to view and download the content on the site solely for your personal, noncommercial use.  You may not reproduce, modify, display, sell, or distribute the content, or use it in any other way for public or commercial purpose. 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you can email us at [estore@globusmail.com](mailto:estore@globusmail.com?cc=ceo@globusmail.com)

Through this document, we wish to make you:

  * Feel at ease while using our websites.
  * Feel confident while sharing information with us.
  * Aware that you may contact us with your questions or concerns about privacy on this website.
  * Aware that by using our websites you are agreeing to the collection of certain data.

**Information that may be collected from you**

www.globus.in collects the details provided by you on registration together with information we learn about you from your use of our service and your visits to our website and other websites accessible from them.

**Kindly, note that www.globus.in does not access or store your Payment Card details (i.e. credit/debit card number, expiration date, CVV etc.). When you make a purchase using your card, all required transaction details are captured on the secured payment page, and are securely transmitted to your card issuer for obtaining an authorization decision. At no time during the purchase process or thereafter does www.globus.in have access to, or store, your complete card account information.**

We may collect additional information in connection with your participation in any promotions or contests offered by us and information you provide when giving us feedback or completing profile forms. We also monitor customer traffic patterns and website use, which enables us to improve the service we provide. We will collect only such information as is necessary and relevant to us to provide you with the services available on the website.

While you use our website, we may have automatic access to (receive and collect) certain anonymous information in standard usage logs through our web server, obtained from “cookies” sent to your browser from web server cookies stored on your hard drive, including:

  * Computer-identification information.
  * IP address, assigned to the computer which you use.
  * The domain server through which you access our service.
  * The type of computer you're using.
  * The type of web browser you're using.

While you are transacting on our website **personally identifiable information** collected about you may include:

  * First and last name. 
  * Email addresses. 
  * Contact details including phone numbers.
  * PIN/ZIP code.
  * Demographic profile (like your age, gender, occupation, education, address and durables owned).
  * Personal preferences and interests (such as books, movies, music and so on); and
  * Your opinion on services, products, features on our websites.

We may also collect the following information about:

  * The pages you visit/access. 
  * The links you click on our website. 
  * The number of times you access the page. 
  * Things you view, add to bag, add to wish list.
  * Other websites you open simultaneously while browsing on ours.

You may terminate your account at any time by writing to us at [estore@globusmail.com](mailto:estore@globusmail.com?cc=ceo@globusmail.com), from the email ID you have used for creating your account login, and mentioning “Please close my www.globus.in account” in the subject line. We will disable access to your account within 4 working days of receiving your mail. However, your information may remain stored in archive on our servers even after the deletion or termination of your account.

**When / How do we collect the information?**

We will collect anonymous traffic information from you when you visit our website.

We collect the personally identifiable information from you when you register with us or you transact as a guest. During registration you are required to give us your contact information (such as name, email address, date of birth, gender, billing address, delivery address, pin code, mobile number, occupation, interests etc.) Upon registration users may receive communications from www.globus.in (e.g. newsletters, updates). Even when you transact as a guest we collect identifiable information (such as name, email address, date of birth, gender, billing address, delivery address, pin code, mobile number etc.).

We use this information to contact you about the services you are using on our website and services in which you have expressed interest.

When you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form, in order to be able to fulfill your requested service. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address).

We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.

You have the option to provide demographic information (such as occupation, education and gender) to us; we encourage you to submit this information so we can provide you a more personalized experience on our website.

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our website, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the website. www.globus.in does store this information and the information is used for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program.

Your friend may contact us at [estore@globusmail.com](mailto:estore@globusmail.com?cc=ceo@globusmail.com) to request that we remove this information from our database.

We are the sole owners of your information collected by us at different points on our Website.

We will collect personally identifiable information about you only as part of a voluntary registration process, guest check out, on-line survey, or contest or any combination thereof.

Our advertisers may collect anonymous traffic information from their own assigned cookies to your browser.

The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such websites which we do not own, manage or control.

We may at certain times make chat rooms, forums, instant messenger and message boards and other services available to you. Please understand that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information. We have no control over its use and you should exercise caution when disclosing your personal information to anyone.

If you use a bulletin board or chat room on this website, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

**How is the information used?**

We use your contact information to send you:

  * Password reminder and registration confirmation. 
  * Special offers. 
  * Changes in the service policies or terms of use. 
  * Event based communications such as order information, renewal notices, invites, reminders etc.

**Note: We send users updates upon registration, and updates regarding your order status. We also send promotional emails to inform you about new arrivals, special offers, etc.**

We use your personal information to:

  * Improve personalized features on our websites to enhance your shopping experience. 
  * To contact you for your account / profile related matters or any other reason as may be necessary. 
  * To provide the services requested by you example deliver merchandise ordered by you. 
  * To preserve social history as governed by existing law or policy. 

**We use anonymous traffic information to:**

  * Remember you in order to deliver better and more personalized service e.g. track your entries in our promotion schemes; 
  * Recognize your usage privileges to our website. 
  * Administer and manage smooth functioning of our website by diagnosing problems. 
  * Track your session and activities so that we can understand better how people use our website. 

**Who do we share your information with?**

We do not share your information with third parties except our agents and alliance partners.

**Agents**  
We use the services of our enabling partners such as outside shipping companies, resellers, business associates to fulfill orders, and credit / debit card processing companies to process the payment for goods and services ordered from www.globus.in website. These entities do not retain, store, share or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes.

**Alliance Partners**   
We will share your information with our alliance partners who work with us or on our behalf to help provide you the services. An alliance partner is a company or an individual who owns and manages (wholly or part of) online content on their websites powered by [www.globus.in](http://www.globus.in/). 

We share email addresses with agents and Alliance partners. The agents and Alliance partners use the email address to confirm the deliveries, send notices and offer services related to the service.  
We do not rent, sell or share your personal information and we will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information to any other third parties unless: 

  * Required by special circumstances such as compliance with subpoenas, court orders, requests/order from legal authorities or law enforcement agencies requiring such disclosure;
  * To help investigate, prevent or take action regarding unlawful and illegal activities, suspected fraud, potential threat to the safety or security of any person, violations of www.globus.in terms of use or to defend against legal claims; 
  * We have your permission;
  * To provide products or services you've requested.

The security of your personal information and email address is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit / debit card number) on our acquiring bank’s system or order forms, they encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). To learn more about SSL, follow this link <http://www.verisign.com/>

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information and email address submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is fully secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information and email address, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our website, you can email us at: [estore@globusmail.com](mailto:estore@globusmail.com?cc=ceo@globusmail.com)

**What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of your information?**

You can accept or decline the cookies. All websites that are customizable require that you accept cookies. You must also accept cookies to register as someone for access to some of our services. For information on how to set your browser to alert you to cookies, or to reject cookies, go to <http://www.cookiecentral.com/>

You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of the website or unable to avail of any of our services. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to our site. 

Cookies

  1. We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration. This is statistical data about how you browse our website. 

  2. For the same reason, we may obtain information about your general Internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive. 
  3. Cookies help us to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more customized service. They enable us: 
    1. To estimate usage numbers and patterns. 
    2. To store information about your preferences, and so allow us to customize our Website according to your individual interests. 
    3. To speed up your searches. 
    4. To recognize you when you return to our site. 

Voluntary disclosure of information.

Supplying personally identifiable information is entirely voluntary. You are not required to register with us in order to use our websites. However, we offer some services only to visitors who do register.

You may change your interests at any time and may opt-in or opt-out of any marketing / promotional / newsletters mailings. www.globus.in reserves the right to send you certain service related communication, considered to be a part of your www.globus.in account without offering you the facility to opt-out. You may update your information and change your account settings at any time.

We provide you with the opportunity to opt-out of having your email address used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information. For example, if you purchase a product / service but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preferences. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by selecting your preferences in “My Account”. If you still face an issue then you may contact us at **022 31920353** or email us at [estore@globusmail.com](mailto:estore@globusmail.com?cc=ceo@globusmail.com)

Upon request, we will remove / block your personally identifiable information from our database, thereby canceling your registration. However, your information may remain stored in archive on our servers even after the deletion or the termination of your account.

If we plan to use your personally identifiable information for any commercial purposes, we will notify you at the time we collect that information and allow you to opt-out of having your information used for those purposes.

**What security procedures are in place to protect information from loss, misuse or alteration?**

To protect your privacy and security, we will verify your identity before granting access or making changes to your personally identifying information. If you have registered your profile on www.globus.in, your www.globus.in ID and Password are required in order to access your profile information.

To protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control, we have in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures. For example, our servers are accessible only to authorized personnel and your information is shared with respective personnel on need to know basis to complete the transaction and to provide the services requested by you. 

Although we will endeavor to safeguard the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information, transmissions made by means of the Internet cannot be made absolutely secure. By using this website, you agree that Globus Stores Pvt Ltd will have no liability for disclosure of your information due to errors in transmission or unauthorized acts of third parties.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

If you have any questions about security on our website, you can email us at [estore@globusmail.com](mailto:estore@globusmail.com?cc=ceo@globusmail.com)

**How can you correct inaccuracies in the information?**

To correct or update any information you have provided, our websites allow you to do it online.

**Policy updates**

We reserve the right to change or update this policy at any time by placing a prominent notice on our website. Such changes shall be effective immediately upon posting to this website. 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, or by means of a notice on our homepage.

You can offer your views, suggestions, if any, by submitting the filled in feedback form online.

**Disclaimer:**

**"We as a merchant shall be under no liability whatsoever in respect of any loss or damage arising directly or indirectly out of the decline of authorization for any Transaction, on Account of the Cardholder having exceeded the preset limit  mutually agreed by us with our acquiring bank from time to time".**

**Contact information**

You can contact us at:   
Globus Stores Pvt Ltd  
Rahejas, Corner Of main Avenue & VP Road,  
Santacruz-W, Mumbai – 400054.  
INDIA.

(022) 26058731 / 32 /33 /34.
